<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Software Engineer | Researcher.</title>
    <link>https://chrberger.github.io/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Software Engineer | Researcher.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 Christian Berger</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://chrberger.github.io/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://chrberger.github.io/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrberger.github.io/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Christian Berger is Full Professor and Docent for Software Engineering at the Department of Computer Science and Engineering at University of Gothenburg, Sweden. His research focuses on systematically architecting complex software and systems embracing continuous integration (CI), continuous deployment (CD), and continuous experimentation (CE) for a growingly automated and digitalized society.
He is an expert for autonomous systems and self-driving vehicles with over a decade of experience:
 Coordinating &amp;ldquo;Team CarOLO&amp;rdquo; (summary|videos) from Technische Universität Braunschweig, Germany - the best European contestant at the 2007 DARPA Urban Challenge Collaborating with Berkeley&amp;rsquo;s Drive Lab (summary) Supervising student teams from Chalmers University of Technology and University of Gothenburg at CaroloCup student competition for self-driving miniature cars: 2013 (first prize), 2014, 2015, 2016, 2017 Supporting &amp;ldquo;Chalmers Truck Team&amp;rdquo; at 2016 Grand Cooperative Driving Challenge (first prize for best HMI) Co-coordinating the research project COPPLAR to develop a self-driving vehicle for urban scenarios Supporting Wallenberg Autonomous Systems and Software Program (WASP) as member of the Graduate School Management Group Autonomous Systems and the Demonstrator Management Group  He is the lead engineer for the world&amp;rsquo;s first single-file, header-only C++ middleware libcluon (docs|tutorials|source|Docker) and jointly leads the design and development of the open source platform Open Driverless Vehicle (OpenDLV) (source|Twitter).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected Publications</title>
      <link>https://chrberger.github.io/home/publications_selected/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrberger.github.io/home/publications_selected/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Publications</title>
      <link>https://chrberger.github.io/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrberger.github.io/home/publications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://chrberger.github.io/home/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrberger.github.io/home/teaching/</guid>
      <description> DIT-022: Mathematical Foundations for Software Engineering at University of Gothenburg, Sweden DIT-638: Cyber-Physical Systems and Systems of Systems at University of Gothenburg, Sweden DIT-168: Industrial IT and Embedded Systems at University of Gothenburg, Sweden 16WS-46041: Generative Aspects of Software Development in the Automotive Domain at RWTH Aachen University, Germany  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://chrberger.github.io/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrberger.github.io/home/contact/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Notice
When accessing this website, a visitor&amp;rsquo;s web-browser is automatically providing information about the resource to be loaded, the IP address to which the resource shall be transferred to, and dependent on a visitor&amp;rsquo;s web-browser potentially information from previous visits. The content for this website is hosted at github.io, a website service provided by GitHub, Inc. Details about their privacy policy can be found here.
The content from this website is provided via github.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
